1
00:01:16,870 --> 00:01:19,160


2
00:01:19,330 --> 00:01:20,910


3
00:01:21,080 --> 00:01:23,830


4
00:01:24,000 --> 00:01:25,750


5
00:01:34,790 --> 00:01:36,080


6
00:01:36,250 --> 00:01:39,620


7
00:01:39,790 --> 00:01:42,950


8
00:01:50,910 --> 00:01:52,160


9
00:01:52,330 --> 00:01:53,950


10
00:01:54,120 --> 00:01:56,410


11
00:01:56,580 --> 00:01:59,080


12
00:01:59,250 --> 00:02:03,200


13
00:02:11,660 --> 00:02:14,290


14
00:02:17,200 --> 00:02:19,250


15
00:02:19,410 --> 00:02:22,910


16
00:02:24,620 --> 00:02:26,370


17
00:02:26,540 --> 00:02:28,910


18
00:02:29,080 --> 00:02:32,450


19
00:02:40,250 --> 00:02:42,700


20
00:02:48,290 --> 00:02:49,370


21
00:03:00,870 --> 00:03:03,790


22
00:03:09,290 --> 00:03:11,660


23
00:03:11,660 --> 00:03:20,620


24
00:03:21,620 --> 00:03:24,620


25
00:03:30,620 --> 00:03:32,750


26
00:03:32,910 --> 00:03:35,410


27
00:03:35,580 --> 00:03:37,580


28
00:03:37,750 --> 00:03:38,790


29
00:03:39,950 --> 00:03:41,750


30
00:03:41,910 --> 00:03:43,370


31
00:03:43,540 --> 00:03:45,290


32
00:03:45,450 --> 00:03:48,250


33
00:03:48,410 --> 00:03:50,370


34
00:03:50,540 --> 00:03:52,040


35
00:03:52,200 --> 00:03:53,410


36
00:03:53,580 --> 00:03:54,910


37
00:03:55,080 --> 00:03:57,410


38
00:03:57,580 --> 00:04:01,250


39
00:04:01,410 --> 00:04:02,870


40
00:04:03,040 --> 00:04:06,750


41
00:04:06,910 --> 00:04:08,500


42
00:04:08,660 --> 00:04:09,910


43
00:04:10,080 --> 00:04:12,040


44
00:04:12,200 --> 00:04:15,950


45
00:04:16,120 --> 00:04:17,540


46
00:04:24,790 --> 00:04:26,750


47
00:04:35,950 --> 00:04:37,540


48
00:04:37,700 --> 00:04:41,290


49
00:04:41,450 --> 00:04:43,830


50
00:04:44,000 --> 00:04:45,830


51
00:04:46,000 --> 00:04:47,500


52
00:04:47,660 --> 00:04:49,830


53
00:04:50,000 --> 00:04:52,620


54
00:04:52,790 --> 00:04:54,250


55
00:04:54,410 --> 00:04:56,580


56
00:04:56,750 --> 00:04:58,290


57
00:04:58,450 --> 00:05:01,750


58
00:05:01,910 --> 00:05:03,830


59
00:05:04,000 --> 00:05:06,330


60
00:05:06,500 --> 00:05:09,450


61
00:05:09,620 --> 00:05:12,200


62
00:05:12,370 --> 00:05:14,490


63
00:05:16,330 --> 00:05:17,290


64
00:05:17,450 --> 00:05:18,700


65
00:05:18,870 --> 00:05:20,160


66
00:05:20,330 --> 00:05:21,790


67
00:05:21,950 --> 00:05:24,790


68
00:05:24,950 --> 00:05:27,790


69
00:05:28,950 --> 00:05:30,330


70
00:05:30,490 --> 00:05:32,740


71
00:05:35,080 --> 00:05:38,080


72
00:05:38,240 --> 00:05:41,040


73
00:05:44,040 --> 00:05:47,040


74
00:05:48,240 --> 00:05:49,450


75
00:05:50,410 --> 00:05:51,870


76
00:05:52,200 --> 00:05:55,910


77
00:05:56,080 --> 00:06:00,080


78
00:06:00,240 --> 00:06:02,370


79
00:06:02,540 --> 00:06:06,330


80
00:06:06,490 --> 00:06:09,660


81
00:06:09,830 --> 00:06:10,870


82
00:06:11,040 --> 00:06:12,910


83
00:06:13,080 --> 00:06:15,740


84
00:06:15,910 --> 00:06:18,660


85
00:06:18,830 --> 00:06:21,330


86
00:06:24,740 --> 00:06:26,660


87
00:06:26,830 --> 00:06:29,240


88
00:06:29,410 --> 00:06:32,870


89
00:06:34,910 --> 00:06:36,830


90
00:06:37,660 --> 00:06:38,830


91
00:06:38,990 --> 00:06:41,620


92
00:06:41,790 --> 00:06:44,080


93
00:06:44,240 --> 00:06:46,990


94
00:06:47,160 --> 00:06:48,490


95
00:06:48,660 --> 00:06:50,040


96
00:06:50,200 --> 00:06:53,200


97
00:06:53,370 --> 00:06:56,120


98
00:06:56,290 --> 00:06:57,540


99
00:06:57,700 --> 00:06:58,870


100
00:06:59,040 --> 00:07:01,120


101
00:07:01,290 --> 00:07:02,700


102
00:07:02,870 --> 00:07:06,080


103
00:07:06,240 --> 00:07:09,580


104
00:07:11,410 --> 00:07:13,540


105
00:07:13,700 --> 00:07:16,540


106
00:07:16,700 --> 00:07:17,740


107
00:07:18,830 --> 00:07:21,830


108
00:07:21,990 --> 00:07:23,950


109
00:07:24,120 --> 00:07:25,490


110
00:07:30,830 --> 00:07:31,870


111
00:07:32,040 --> 00:07:35,910


112
00:07:36,080 --> 00:07:37,540


113
00:07:37,700 --> 00:07:41,540


114
00:07:41,700 --> 00:07:44,700


115
00:07:47,870 --> 00:07:50,620


116
00:07:50,790 --> 00:07:53,540


117
00:07:53,700 --> 00:07:55,790


118
00:07:55,950 --> 00:07:57,830


119
00:07:57,990 --> 00:08:00,660


120
00:08:00,830 --> 00:08:02,370


121
00:08:02,540 --> 00:08:04,490


122
00:08:04,660 --> 00:08:06,990


123
00:08:07,160 --> 00:08:09,950


124
00:08:10,120 --> 00:08:12,910


125
00:08:13,080 --> 00:08:15,120


126
00:08:15,290 --> 00:08:16,410


127
00:08:16,580 --> 00:08:18,660


128
00:08:18,830 --> 00:08:21,740


129
00:08:21,910 --> 00:08:25,200


130
00:08:26,120 --> 00:08:28,790


131
00:08:28,950 --> 00:08:31,160


132
00:08:31,330 --> 00:08:33,330


133
00:08:33,490 --> 00:08:35,080


134
00:08:35,240 --> 00:08:37,910


135
00:08:40,160 --> 00:08:41,660


136
00:08:41,830 --> 00:08:45,540


137
00:08:49,450 --> 00:08:51,540


138
00:08:51,700 --> 00:08:54,120


139
00:08:54,290 --> 00:08:55,580


140
00:08:56,660 --> 00:08:58,540


141
00:08:59,790 --> 00:09:02,290


142
00:09:02,450 --> 00:09:04,450


143
00:09:04,620 --> 00:09:06,950


144
00:09:07,120 --> 00:09:09,240


145
00:09:09,450 --> 00:09:10,790


146
00:09:10,950 --> 00:09:12,700


147
00:09:12,870 --> 00:09:15,410


148
00:09:15,580 --> 00:09:17,910


149
00:09:18,080 --> 00:09:20,620


150
00:09:22,870 --> 00:09:25,450


151
00:09:25,660 --> 00:09:27,290


152
00:09:27,450 --> 00:09:30,200


153
00:09:30,410 --> 00:09:33,410


154
00:09:33,580 --> 00:09:35,080


155
00:09:35,240 --> 00:09:37,910


156
00:09:39,040 --> 00:09:41,580


157
00:09:41,790 --> 00:09:43,330


158
00:09:43,540 --> 00:09:46,950


159
00:09:47,160 --> 00:09:50,240


160
00:09:50,410 --> 00:09:52,120


161
00:09:52,330 --> 00:09:53,990


162
00:09:54,200 --> 00:09:56,120


163
00:09:56,330 --> 00:09:59,240


164
00:09:59,450 --> 00:10:02,870


165
00:10:03,080 --> 00:10:06,490


166
00:10:09,490 --> 00:10:12,330


167
00:10:14,040 --> 00:10:17,410


168
00:10:17,620 --> 00:10:19,910


169
00:10:20,990 --> 00:10:24,080


170
00:10:24,240 --> 00:10:26,450


171
00:10:27,410 --> 00:10:31,450


172
00:10:31,660 --> 00:10:34,080


173
00:10:34,290 --> 00:10:36,830


174
00:10:38,370 --> 00:10:41,700


175
00:10:42,540 --> 00:10:44,790


176
00:10:47,290 --> 00:10:48,660


177
00:10:48,870 --> 00:10:51,540


178
00:11:04,580 --> 00:11:07,240


179
00:11:07,410 --> 00:11:10,660


180
00:11:10,870 --> 00:11:13,160


181
00:11:13,370 --> 00:11:16,120


182
00:11:16,290 --> 00:11:18,740


183
00:11:18,910 --> 00:11:22,330


184
00:11:22,490 --> 00:11:25,740


185
00:11:25,950 --> 00:11:29,990


186
00:11:32,830 --> 00:11:36,330


187
00:11:36,540 --> 00:11:38,330


188
00:11:38,490 --> 00:11:40,200


189
00:11:40,410 --> 00:11:41,790


190
00:11:41,950 --> 00:11:44,660


191
00:11:44,830 --> 00:11:47,040


192
00:11:47,240 --> 00:11:52,370


193
00:11:52,580 --> 00:11:54,120


194
00:11:54,290 --> 00:11:57,410


195
00:12:03,240 --> 00:12:05,370


196
00:12:05,580 --> 00:12:10,040


197
00:12:10,200 --> 00:12:13,580


198
00:12:13,740 --> 00:12:17,330


199
00:12:17,540 --> 00:12:20,080


200
00:12:20,240 --> 00:12:23,490


201
00:12:23,660 --> 00:12:26,620


202
00:12:29,240 --> 00:12:31,620


203
00:12:43,910 --> 00:12:46,160


204
00:12:46,330 --> 00:12:49,370


205
00:12:49,540 --> 00:12:51,370


206
00:12:51,540 --> 00:12:56,040


207
00:12:56,200 --> 00:12:58,740


208
00:12:58,910 --> 00:13:00,450


209
00:13:00,620 --> 00:13:01,740


210
00:13:01,910 --> 00:13:03,450


211
00:13:03,620 --> 00:13:05,660


212
00:13:05,830 --> 00:13:07,370


213
00:13:07,540 --> 00:13:09,660


214
00:13:09,830 --> 00:13:11,160


215
00:13:12,790 --> 00:13:14,990


216
00:13:17,370 --> 00:13:18,990


217
00:13:19,160 --> 00:13:20,740


218
00:13:22,910 --> 00:13:25,490


219
00:13:25,660 --> 00:13:27,040


220
00:13:30,290 --> 00:13:32,040


221
00:13:32,200 --> 00:13:33,540


222
00:13:33,700 --> 00:13:35,660


223
00:13:35,830 --> 00:13:37,830


224
00:13:37,990 --> 00:13:40,490


225
00:13:40,660 --> 00:13:42,370


226
00:13:42,540 --> 00:13:43,740


227
00:13:43,910 --> 00:13:46,830


228
00:13:47,740 --> 00:13:48,910


229
00:13:49,080 --> 00:13:50,330


230
00:13:50,490 --> 00:13:54,410


231
00:13:54,580 --> 00:13:57,950


232
00:13:58,120 --> 00:14:00,950


233
00:14:01,120 --> 00:14:04,370


234
00:14:08,080 --> 00:14:10,370


235
00:14:10,540 --> 00:14:12,870


236
00:14:28,830 --> 00:14:31,990


237
00:14:32,160 --> 00:14:36,120


238
00:14:36,290 --> 00:14:39,450


239
00:14:39,620 --> 00:14:40,870


240
00:14:41,040 --> 00:14:44,040


241
00:14:44,200 --> 00:14:46,620


242
00:14:46,790 --> 00:14:48,330


243
00:14:48,490 --> 00:14:50,040


244
00:14:50,200 --> 00:14:52,990


245
00:14:56,540 --> 00:14:58,790


246
00:15:02,410 --> 00:15:07,040


247
00:15:07,200 --> 00:15:09,330


248
00:15:09,490 --> 00:15:11,660


249
00:15:11,830 --> 00:15:13,540


250
00:15:13,700 --> 00:15:14,830


251
00:15:14,990 --> 00:15:17,740


252
00:15:17,910 --> 00:15:20,660


253
00:15:20,830 --> 00:15:22,910


254
00:15:23,080 --> 00:15:24,870


255
00:15:25,040 --> 00:15:26,410


256
00:15:26,580 --> 00:15:28,370


257
00:15:28,540 --> 00:15:29,830


258
00:15:29,990 --> 00:15:32,740


259
00:15:32,910 --> 00:15:34,450


260
00:15:34,620 --> 00:15:36,790


261
00:15:36,950 --> 00:15:38,870


262
00:15:39,040 --> 00:15:40,790


263
00:15:40,950 --> 00:15:43,580


264
00:15:43,740 --> 00:15:45,040


265
00:15:45,200 --> 00:15:47,240


266
00:15:47,410 --> 00:15:48,620


267
00:15:48,790 --> 00:15:50,080


268
00:15:50,240 --> 00:15:52,160


269
00:15:52,330 --> 00:15:55,870


270
00:15:56,040 --> 00:15:58,410


271
00:15:58,580 --> 00:16:01,660


272
00:16:01,830 --> 00:16:04,830


273
00:16:04,990 --> 00:16:06,660


274
00:16:06,830 --> 00:16:09,450


275
00:16:09,620 --> 00:16:12,450


276
00:16:16,080 --> 00:16:17,200


277
00:16:34,200 --> 00:16:37,410


278
00:16:37,580 --> 00:16:40,620


279
00:16:42,290 --> 00:16:43,870


280
00:16:44,040 --> 00:16:46,790


281
00:16:46,950 --> 00:16:48,620


282
00:16:48,790 --> 00:16:51,040


283
00:16:51,200 --> 00:16:52,740


284
00:16:52,910 --> 00:16:56,290


285
00:16:56,450 --> 00:16:59,240


286
00:16:59,410 --> 00:17:03,290


287
00:17:03,450 --> 00:17:05,450


288
00:17:05,620 --> 00:17:07,120


289
00:17:07,290 --> 00:17:09,240


290
00:17:09,410 --> 00:17:12,290


291
00:17:12,450 --> 00:17:14,540


292
00:17:14,700 --> 00:17:16,580


293
00:17:16,740 --> 00:17:18,700


294
00:17:18,870 --> 00:17:20,700


295
00:17:20,870 --> 00:17:21,990


296
00:17:22,160 --> 00:17:24,660


297
00:17:24,830 --> 00:17:26,410


298
00:17:26,580 --> 00:17:29,040


299
00:17:29,200 --> 00:17:30,410


300
00:17:30,580 --> 00:17:32,330


301
00:17:32,490 --> 00:17:33,950


302
00:17:34,120 --> 00:17:37,040


303
00:17:38,240 --> 00:17:39,700


304
00:17:39,870 --> 00:17:42,870


305
00:17:43,040 --> 00:17:44,870


306
00:17:45,040 --> 00:17:46,620


307
00:17:46,790 --> 00:17:49,740


308
00:17:49,910 --> 00:17:51,200


309
00:17:51,370 --> 00:17:54,240


310
00:17:54,410 --> 00:17:56,240


311
00:18:00,830 --> 00:18:03,910


312
00:18:04,080 --> 00:18:07,040


313
00:18:07,200 --> 00:18:10,040


314
00:18:10,200 --> 00:18:11,870


315
00:18:12,040 --> 00:18:15,950


316
00:18:16,790 --> 00:18:20,040


317
00:18:20,200 --> 00:18:23,040


318
00:18:25,160 --> 00:18:26,660


319
00:18:26,830 --> 00:18:29,200


320
00:18:29,370 --> 00:18:31,370


321
00:18:31,540 --> 00:18:34,580


322
00:18:34,740 --> 00:18:36,540


323
00:18:36,700 --> 00:18:39,450


324
00:18:39,620 --> 00:18:41,450


325
00:18:41,620 --> 00:18:44,370


326
00:18:44,540 --> 00:18:46,080


327
00:18:46,240 --> 00:18:48,740


328
00:18:48,910 --> 00:18:50,830


329
00:18:50,990 --> 00:18:52,370


330
00:18:52,540 --> 00:18:56,040


331
00:18:56,200 --> 00:18:59,490


332
00:18:59,660 --> 00:19:03,200


333
00:19:03,370 --> 00:19:05,540


334
00:19:05,700 --> 00:19:08,160


335
00:19:08,330 --> 00:19:10,660


336
00:19:10,830 --> 00:19:12,990


337
00:19:13,160 --> 00:19:17,580


338
00:19:17,740 --> 00:19:20,490


339
00:19:38,240 --> 00:19:40,660


340
00:19:40,830 --> 00:19:44,160


341
00:19:44,330 --> 00:19:46,040


342
00:19:46,200 --> 00:19:48,700


343
00:19:48,870 --> 00:19:50,450


344
00:19:50,620 --> 00:19:51,660


345
00:19:51,830 --> 00:19:54,580


346
00:19:54,740 --> 00:19:56,870


347
00:19:57,040 --> 00:19:59,580


348
00:19:59,740 --> 00:20:02,200


349
00:20:02,370 --> 00:20:03,990


350
00:20:05,660 --> 00:20:07,660


351
00:20:07,830 --> 00:20:10,870


352
00:20:11,040 --> 00:20:13,040


353
00:20:13,200 --> 00:20:14,870


354
00:20:15,040 --> 00:20:18,540


355
00:20:18,700 --> 00:20:20,580


356
00:20:20,740 --> 00:20:22,540


357
00:20:22,700 --> 00:20:26,290


358
00:20:27,790 --> 00:20:28,830


359
00:20:28,990 --> 00:20:30,990


360
00:20:31,160 --> 00:20:33,740


361
00:20:33,910 --> 00:20:35,870


362
00:20:36,040 --> 00:20:37,950


363
00:20:38,120 --> 00:20:39,160


364
00:20:39,330 --> 00:20:42,160


365
00:20:54,080 --> 00:20:57,120


366
00:21:04,040 --> 00:21:07,540


367
00:21:07,700 --> 00:21:11,450


368
00:21:11,620 --> 00:21:14,740


369
00:21:14,910 --> 00:21:18,160


370
00:21:18,330 --> 00:21:22,200


371
00:21:22,370 --> 00:21:25,830


372
00:21:25,990 --> 00:21:29,040


373
00:21:29,200 --> 00:21:34,040


374
00:21:35,790 --> 00:21:37,370


375
00:21:37,540 --> 00:21:41,160


376
00:21:42,660 --> 00:21:44,540


377
00:21:46,580 --> 00:21:48,120


378
00:21:51,160 --> 00:21:52,580


379
00:21:58,410 --> 00:21:59,990


380
00:22:00,870 --> 00:22:04,700


381
00:22:04,910 --> 00:22:07,240


382
00:22:07,410 --> 00:22:08,990


383
00:22:09,200 --> 00:22:10,490


384
00:22:10,700 --> 00:22:13,580


385
00:22:13,740 --> 00:22:16,240


386
00:22:16,450 --> 00:22:18,910


387
00:22:19,120 --> 00:22:21,490


388
00:22:21,700 --> 00:22:23,580


389
00:22:23,790 --> 00:22:26,450


390
00:22:26,660 --> 00:22:27,950


391
00:22:28,160 --> 00:22:30,290


392
00:22:35,740 --> 00:22:37,200


393
00:22:37,410 --> 00:22:41,450


394
00:22:41,660 --> 00:22:44,080


395
00:22:44,280 --> 00:22:46,870


396
00:22:47,080 --> 00:22:50,080


397
00:22:52,530 --> 00:22:55,530


398
00:22:55,740 --> 00:22:57,950


399
00:23:00,370 --> 00:23:03,530


400
00:23:03,700 --> 00:23:05,990


401
00:23:11,490 --> 00:23:13,120


402
00:23:15,280 --> 00:23:16,990


403
00:23:22,620 --> 00:23:24,660


404
00:23:24,870 --> 00:23:26,490


405
00:23:35,490 --> 00:23:37,280


406
00:23:37,490 --> 00:23:39,950


407
00:23:41,330 --> 00:23:44,410


408
00:23:44,580 --> 00:23:48,080


409
00:23:48,240 --> 00:23:49,410


410
00:23:49,580 --> 00:23:52,030


411
00:23:55,200 --> 00:23:56,740


412
00:23:58,740 --> 00:24:00,370


413
00:24:00,530 --> 00:24:02,830


414
00:24:02,990 --> 00:24:05,700


415
00:24:05,870 --> 00:24:08,870


416
00:24:09,080 --> 00:24:11,280


417
00:24:11,490 --> 00:24:14,740


418
00:24:14,910 --> 00:24:19,280


419
00:24:19,490 --> 00:24:22,120


420
00:24:22,280 --> 00:24:25,700


421
00:24:25,870 --> 00:24:27,410


422
00:24:27,580 --> 00:24:30,740


423
00:24:32,620 --> 00:24:34,660


424
00:24:34,830 --> 00:24:37,490


425
00:24:37,660 --> 00:24:39,870


426
00:24:43,030 --> 00:24:46,160


427
00:24:46,330 --> 00:24:47,870


428
00:24:48,030 --> 00:24:52,490


429
00:24:52,660 --> 00:24:55,830


430
00:24:55,990 --> 00:24:58,780


431
00:24:58,950 --> 00:25:01,660


432
00:25:02,450 --> 00:25:04,740


433
00:25:04,950 --> 00:25:07,160


434
00:25:07,330 --> 00:25:09,950


435
00:25:10,120 --> 00:25:14,450


436
00:25:14,620 --> 00:25:17,740


437
00:25:20,120 --> 00:25:21,780


438
00:25:25,160 --> 00:25:27,450


439
00:25:27,620 --> 00:25:29,740


440
00:25:29,910 --> 00:25:31,830


441
00:25:33,870 --> 00:25:36,700


442
00:25:36,870 --> 00:25:38,990


443
00:25:40,370 --> 00:25:41,950


444
00:25:42,120 --> 00:25:44,200


445
00:25:44,370 --> 00:25:46,830


446
00:25:50,080 --> 00:25:51,240


447
00:25:52,280 --> 00:25:54,530


448
00:25:54,700 --> 00:25:57,530


449
00:25:58,280 --> 00:26:01,660


450
00:26:01,830 --> 00:26:04,200


451
00:26:09,780 --> 00:26:12,410


452
00:26:12,580 --> 00:26:13,950


453
00:26:14,120 --> 00:26:16,330


454
00:26:18,580 --> 00:26:20,830


455
00:26:20,990 --> 00:26:25,410


456
00:26:25,580 --> 00:26:28,490


457
00:26:29,330 --> 00:26:31,080


458
00:26:32,910 --> 00:26:34,490


459
00:26:34,660 --> 00:26:36,120


460
00:26:37,280 --> 00:26:38,530


461
00:26:38,700 --> 00:26:40,450


462
00:26:40,620 --> 00:26:42,740


463
00:26:42,910 --> 00:26:44,200


464
00:26:44,370 --> 00:26:45,490


465
00:26:45,660 --> 00:26:49,240


466
00:26:49,410 --> 00:26:51,330


467
00:26:51,490 --> 00:26:53,740


468
00:26:53,910 --> 00:26:55,530


469
00:26:55,700 --> 00:26:58,160


470
00:26:58,330 --> 00:27:01,080


471
00:27:01,240 --> 00:27:02,780


472
00:27:02,950 --> 00:27:04,780


473
00:27:04,950 --> 00:27:07,080


474
00:27:07,240 --> 00:27:10,160


475
00:27:10,330 --> 00:27:12,160


476
00:27:12,330 --> 00:27:15,160


477
00:27:15,330 --> 00:27:18,990


478
00:27:19,160 --> 00:27:22,830


479
00:27:22,990 --> 00:27:24,700


480
00:27:24,870 --> 00:27:26,530


481
00:27:26,700 --> 00:27:28,370


482
00:27:28,530 --> 00:27:32,740


483
00:27:34,120 --> 00:27:38,280


484
00:27:40,120 --> 00:27:41,330


485
00:27:41,490 --> 00:27:43,910


486
00:27:44,080 --> 00:27:45,120


487
00:27:45,280 --> 00:27:47,660


488
00:27:47,830 --> 00:27:50,080


489
00:27:50,240 --> 00:27:53,990


490
00:27:55,160 --> 00:27:57,120


491
00:27:57,280 --> 00:27:59,620


492
00:28:00,370 --> 00:28:02,330


493
00:28:02,490 --> 00:28:05,580


494
00:28:22,330 --> 00:28:25,240


495
00:28:29,950 --> 00:28:31,450


496
00:28:31,620 --> 00:28:34,240


497
00:28:34,410 --> 00:28:37,990


498
00:28:38,160 --> 00:28:41,740


499
00:28:41,910 --> 00:28:45,780


500
00:28:45,950 --> 00:28:51,120


501
00:28:51,280 --> 00:28:54,950


502
00:28:55,120 --> 00:28:57,780


503
00:28:57,950 --> 00:29:00,780


504
00:29:00,950 --> 00:29:02,950


505
00:29:03,120 --> 00:29:06,910


506
00:29:08,370 --> 00:29:10,950


507
00:29:14,410 --> 00:29:16,200


508
00:29:16,370 --> 00:29:19,870


509
00:29:20,030 --> 00:29:23,830


510
00:29:23,990 --> 00:29:26,530


511
00:29:26,700 --> 00:29:29,370


512
00:29:29,530 --> 00:29:31,200


513
00:29:31,370 --> 00:29:33,450


514
00:29:33,620 --> 00:29:36,200


515
00:29:36,370 --> 00:29:38,530


516
00:29:38,700 --> 00:29:42,580


517
00:29:42,740 --> 00:29:45,830


518
00:29:47,830 --> 00:29:49,580


519
00:29:49,740 --> 00:29:51,370


520
00:29:51,530 --> 00:29:54,120


521
00:29:55,620 --> 00:29:57,740


522
00:29:57,910 --> 00:30:00,410


523
00:30:00,580 --> 00:30:03,240


524
00:30:06,580 --> 00:30:08,700


525
00:30:10,870 --> 00:30:12,990


526
00:30:13,160 --> 00:30:15,120


527
00:30:16,280 --> 00:30:18,990


528
00:30:19,160 --> 00:30:21,530


529
00:30:21,700 --> 00:30:24,200


530
00:30:24,370 --> 00:30:26,830


531
00:30:26,990 --> 00:30:29,740


532
00:30:29,910 --> 00:30:32,580


533
00:30:34,740 --> 00:30:36,530


534
00:30:38,030 --> 00:30:41,450


535
00:30:41,620 --> 00:30:45,030


536
00:30:45,200 --> 00:30:47,240


537
00:30:47,410 --> 00:30:50,200


538
00:30:51,410 --> 00:30:54,910


539
00:30:55,080 --> 00:30:57,280


540
00:31:00,370 --> 00:31:03,370


541
00:31:03,530 --> 00:31:05,030


542
00:31:05,200 --> 00:31:08,740


543
00:31:09,950 --> 00:31:11,410


544
00:31:11,580 --> 00:31:14,530


545
00:31:14,700 --> 00:31:16,660


546
00:31:24,780 --> 00:31:28,030


547
00:31:28,200 --> 00:31:29,950


548
00:31:30,120 --> 00:31:33,030


549
00:31:33,660 --> 00:31:36,370


550
00:31:36,530 --> 00:31:37,950


551
00:31:38,120 --> 00:31:41,370


552
00:31:41,530 --> 00:31:45,280


553
00:31:45,450 --> 00:31:48,910


554
00:31:49,080 --> 00:31:52,620


555
00:31:52,780 --> 00:31:55,240


556
00:31:57,700 --> 00:31:59,030


557
00:31:59,200 --> 00:32:01,080


558
00:32:01,240 --> 00:32:03,410


559
00:32:03,580 --> 00:32:06,950


560
00:32:07,120 --> 00:32:08,700


561
00:32:08,870 --> 00:32:11,830


562
00:32:11,990 --> 00:32:14,700


563
00:32:14,870 --> 00:32:17,950


564
00:32:22,530 --> 00:32:24,780


565
00:32:24,950 --> 00:32:27,080


566
00:32:27,240 --> 00:32:31,160


567
00:32:32,580 --> 00:32:34,780


568
00:32:34,950 --> 00:32:36,910


569
00:32:37,080 --> 00:32:38,740


570
00:32:38,910 --> 00:32:42,120


571
00:32:42,280 --> 00:32:44,330


572
00:32:44,490 --> 00:32:46,160


573
00:32:46,330 --> 00:32:48,330


574
00:32:49,490 --> 00:32:50,530


575
00:32:50,700 --> 00:32:51,870


576
00:32:55,990 --> 00:32:58,240


577
00:32:58,410 --> 00:33:01,280


578
00:33:11,830 --> 00:33:13,700


579
00:33:13,870 --> 00:33:15,490


580
00:33:15,660 --> 00:33:19,160


581
00:33:19,330 --> 00:33:21,910


582
00:33:22,080 --> 00:33:23,910


583
00:33:24,080 --> 00:33:26,240


584
00:33:26,410 --> 00:33:28,080


585
00:33:28,240 --> 00:33:31,620


586
00:33:31,780 --> 00:33:36,370


587
00:33:36,530 --> 00:33:37,910


588
00:33:38,080 --> 00:33:41,490


589
00:33:41,660 --> 00:33:43,120


590
00:33:43,280 --> 00:33:46,450


591
00:33:47,780 --> 00:33:51,080


592
00:33:51,240 --> 00:33:54,240


593
00:33:54,410 --> 00:33:55,620


594
00:33:55,780 --> 00:33:58,620


595
00:33:58,780 --> 00:34:00,620


596
00:34:02,280 --> 00:34:05,620


597
00:34:05,780 --> 00:34:07,700


598
00:34:07,870 --> 00:34:10,240


599
00:34:10,410 --> 00:34:12,620


600
00:34:13,700 --> 00:34:15,240


601
00:34:15,410 --> 00:34:16,700


602
00:34:16,870 --> 00:34:18,660


603
00:34:18,830 --> 00:34:21,910


604
00:34:22,080 --> 00:34:26,620


605
00:34:26,830 --> 00:34:29,240


606
00:34:29,410 --> 00:34:31,740


607
00:34:31,910 --> 00:34:33,240


608
00:34:34,410 --> 00:34:35,620


609
00:34:43,990 --> 00:34:46,780


610
00:34:46,990 --> 00:34:47,990


611
00:34:51,490 --> 00:34:53,780


612
00:34:55,280 --> 00:34:57,120


613
00:34:57,330 --> 00:35:00,450


614
00:35:00,660 --> 00:35:03,410


615
00:35:03,620 --> 00:35:05,080


616
00:35:05,240 --> 00:35:07,120


617
00:35:07,330 --> 00:35:11,620


618
00:35:11,830 --> 00:35:15,620


619
00:35:16,780 --> 00:35:19,330


620
00:35:26,950 --> 00:35:30,580


621
00:35:30,780 --> 00:35:33,700


622
00:35:35,330 --> 00:35:37,120


623
00:35:51,200 --> 00:35:53,580


624
00:35:53,780 --> 00:35:56,450


625
00:35:56,660 --> 00:35:58,280


626
00:35:58,490 --> 00:36:00,280


627
00:36:00,490 --> 00:36:02,120


628
00:36:02,330 --> 00:36:04,200


629
00:36:04,370 --> 00:36:07,530


630
00:36:07,700 --> 00:36:10,700


631
00:36:10,870 --> 00:36:12,410


632
00:36:29,200 --> 00:36:32,370


633
00:36:34,580 --> 00:36:37,830


634
00:36:37,990 --> 00:36:40,530


635
00:36:40,740 --> 00:36:43,280


636
00:36:52,080 --> 00:36:53,330


637
00:36:53,530 --> 00:36:55,490


638
00:36:55,700 --> 00:36:57,280


639
00:36:57,450 --> 00:37:00,410


640
00:37:00,580 --> 00:37:03,660


641
00:37:03,870 --> 00:37:05,990


642
00:37:06,620 --> 00:37:09,620


643
00:37:10,830 --> 00:37:12,830


644
00:37:13,450 --> 00:37:14,450


645
00:37:14,660 --> 00:37:16,620


646
00:37:16,780 --> 00:37:18,490


647
00:37:18,700 --> 00:37:21,620


648
00:37:21,780 --> 00:37:24,490


649
00:37:24,660 --> 00:37:28,240


650
00:37:28,450 --> 00:37:29,950


651
00:37:30,120 --> 00:37:32,240


652
00:37:32,410 --> 00:37:35,410


653
00:37:35,580 --> 00:37:39,240


654
00:37:39,450 --> 00:37:41,080


655
00:37:41,240 --> 00:37:43,030


656
00:37:43,200 --> 00:37:46,160


657
00:37:46,330 --> 00:37:48,990


658
00:37:49,160 --> 00:37:50,160


659
00:37:50,370 --> 00:37:52,530


660
00:37:52,700 --> 00:37:54,580


661
00:37:54,740 --> 00:37:57,410


662
00:37:57,580 --> 00:38:00,990


663
00:38:01,160 --> 00:38:05,450


664
00:38:05,620 --> 00:38:08,780


665
00:38:08,950 --> 00:38:11,490


666
00:38:11,660 --> 00:38:13,450


667
00:38:14,700 --> 00:38:17,580


668
00:38:17,740 --> 00:38:20,530


669
00:38:20,700 --> 00:38:21,740


670
00:38:21,910 --> 00:38:24,490


671
00:38:56,160 --> 00:38:57,200


672
00:38:57,370 --> 00:39:00,240


673
00:39:01,870 --> 00:39:03,370


674
00:39:03,530 --> 00:39:06,160


675
00:39:06,330 --> 00:39:08,410


676
00:39:08,580 --> 00:39:10,910


677
00:39:11,080 --> 00:39:14,200


678
00:39:16,490 --> 00:39:18,830


679
00:39:18,990 --> 00:39:21,490


680
00:39:21,660 --> 00:39:25,370


681
00:39:25,530 --> 00:39:28,490


682
00:39:28,660 --> 00:39:30,830


683
00:39:30,990 --> 00:39:32,370


684
00:39:32,530 --> 00:39:36,870


685
00:39:38,330 --> 00:39:42,370


686
00:39:43,330 --> 00:39:45,620


687
00:39:45,780 --> 00:39:47,120


688
00:39:47,280 --> 00:39:49,660


689
00:39:49,830 --> 00:39:54,450


690
00:39:54,620 --> 00:39:57,080


691
00:39:57,240 --> 00:39:58,780


692
00:39:58,950 --> 00:40:02,950


693
00:40:05,120 --> 00:40:07,740


694
00:40:07,910 --> 00:40:11,240


695
00:40:11,410 --> 00:40:15,280


696
00:40:15,450 --> 00:40:18,490


697
00:40:18,660 --> 00:40:20,320


698
00:40:20,490 --> 00:40:24,660


699
00:40:24,820 --> 00:40:26,530


700
00:40:26,700 --> 00:40:28,820


701
00:40:28,990 --> 00:40:31,120


702
00:40:31,280 --> 00:40:33,280


703
00:40:33,450 --> 00:40:34,820


704
00:40:34,990 --> 00:40:37,700


705
00:40:37,870 --> 00:40:39,490


706
00:40:39,660 --> 00:40:42,240


707
00:40:42,410 --> 00:40:45,490


708
00:40:46,660 --> 00:40:50,910


709
00:40:51,070 --> 00:40:53,120


710
00:40:53,950 --> 00:40:56,240


711
00:40:56,410 --> 00:40:59,370


712
00:40:59,530 --> 00:41:01,370


713
00:41:01,530 --> 00:41:03,700


714
00:41:03,870 --> 00:41:06,410


715
00:41:06,570 --> 00:41:08,620


716
00:41:08,780 --> 00:41:11,950


717
00:41:12,120 --> 00:41:14,120


718
00:41:16,570 --> 00:41:18,320


719
00:41:50,160 --> 00:41:52,320


720
00:41:52,490 --> 00:41:54,820


721
00:41:54,990 --> 00:41:57,990


722
00:42:00,570 --> 00:42:03,740


723
00:42:07,660 --> 00:42:10,820


724
00:42:11,740 --> 00:42:13,200


725
00:42:13,370 --> 00:42:15,450


726
00:42:15,620 --> 00:42:17,450


727
00:42:17,620 --> 00:42:20,950


728
00:42:21,120 --> 00:42:23,700


729
00:42:23,870 --> 00:42:25,820


730
00:42:27,530 --> 00:42:29,740


731
00:42:29,910 --> 00:42:34,320


732
00:42:34,490 --> 00:42:36,700


733
00:42:36,870 --> 00:42:39,570


734
00:42:39,740 --> 00:42:42,950


735
00:42:43,120 --> 00:42:45,030


736
00:42:45,200 --> 00:42:47,160


737
00:42:47,990 --> 00:42:50,700


738
00:42:50,870 --> 00:42:53,320


739
00:42:53,490 --> 00:42:55,990


740
00:42:56,160 --> 00:42:58,780


741
00:42:58,950 --> 00:43:01,030


742
00:43:01,200 --> 00:43:03,620


743
00:43:03,780 --> 00:43:05,660


744
00:43:05,820 --> 00:43:08,280


745
00:43:08,990 --> 00:43:11,160


746
00:43:12,740 --> 00:43:14,820


747
00:43:14,990 --> 00:43:16,910


748
00:43:17,070 --> 00:43:18,820


749
00:43:18,990 --> 00:43:20,780


750
00:43:20,950 --> 00:43:23,870


751
00:43:24,030 --> 00:43:25,490


752
00:43:25,660 --> 00:43:27,780


753
00:43:27,950 --> 00:43:29,490


754
00:43:29,660 --> 00:43:30,990


755
00:43:31,160 --> 00:43:33,030


756
00:43:33,200 --> 00:43:36,570


757
00:43:37,530 --> 00:43:39,410


758
00:43:39,570 --> 00:43:41,160


759
00:43:41,320 --> 00:43:43,620


760
00:43:46,200 --> 00:43:47,570


761
00:43:50,950 --> 00:43:52,490


762
00:43:52,660 --> 00:43:54,030


763
00:43:54,200 --> 00:43:57,320


764
00:43:58,780 --> 00:44:01,240


765
00:44:05,490 --> 00:44:06,820


766
00:44:06,990 --> 00:44:09,030


767
00:44:10,660 --> 00:44:13,120


768
00:44:13,280 --> 00:44:14,780


769
00:44:14,950 --> 00:44:16,990


770
00:44:17,160 --> 00:44:18,570


771
00:44:26,280 --> 00:44:29,320


772
00:44:29,490 --> 00:44:32,740


773
00:44:32,910 --> 00:44:36,240


774
00:44:36,410 --> 00:44:39,030


775
00:44:39,200 --> 00:44:42,160


776
00:44:48,740 --> 00:44:52,410


777
00:44:52,570 --> 00:44:55,660


778
00:44:55,820 --> 00:44:58,870


779
00:44:59,030 --> 00:45:01,910


780
00:45:02,070 --> 00:45:04,780


781
00:45:07,910 --> 00:45:10,570


782
00:45:14,950 --> 00:45:16,620


783
00:45:18,700 --> 00:45:22,240


784
00:45:22,410 --> 00:45:24,370


785
00:45:24,530 --> 00:45:26,450


786
00:45:27,370 --> 00:45:28,870


787
00:45:29,030 --> 00:45:31,070


788
00:45:31,240 --> 00:45:32,280


789
00:45:32,450 --> 00:45:35,450


790
00:45:35,620 --> 00:45:36,870


791
00:45:39,740 --> 00:45:42,950


792
00:45:43,120 --> 00:45:44,950


793
00:45:45,120 --> 00:45:48,910


794
00:45:49,070 --> 00:45:50,740


795
00:45:50,910 --> 00:45:52,780


796
00:45:52,950 --> 00:45:55,030


797
00:46:00,200 --> 00:46:03,160


798
00:46:03,320 --> 00:46:05,410


799
00:46:05,570 --> 00:46:07,490


800
00:46:09,200 --> 00:46:10,240


801
00:46:10,410 --> 00:46:12,490


802
00:46:12,660 --> 00:46:15,450


803
00:46:15,620 --> 00:46:17,700


804
00:46:18,780 --> 00:46:20,910


805
00:46:23,120 --> 00:46:25,030


806
00:46:27,450 --> 00:46:29,620


807
00:46:32,070 --> 00:46:33,490


808
00:46:34,410 --> 00:46:36,240


809
00:46:36,410 --> 00:46:39,530


810
00:46:39,700 --> 00:46:41,530


811
00:46:41,700 --> 00:46:44,320


812
00:46:44,490 --> 00:46:48,200


813
00:46:48,410 --> 00:46:49,990


814
00:46:50,160 --> 00:46:52,450


815
00:46:56,990 --> 00:46:59,160


816
00:46:59,320 --> 00:47:01,240


817
00:47:04,660 --> 00:47:06,450


818
00:47:07,570 --> 00:47:10,320


819
00:47:26,030 --> 00:47:29,030


820
00:47:29,240 --> 00:47:31,280


821
00:47:32,120 --> 00:47:34,070


822
00:47:34,280 --> 00:47:37,990


823
00:47:38,200 --> 00:47:39,660


824
00:47:39,820 --> 00:47:41,620


825
00:47:41,780 --> 00:47:44,200


826
00:47:44,410 --> 00:47:47,700


827
00:47:47,910 --> 00:47:52,450


828
00:47:52,660 --> 00:47:55,910


829
00:47:56,950 --> 00:47:57,950


830
00:47:58,160 --> 00:48:02,700


831
00:48:05,280 --> 00:48:07,370


832
00:48:08,740 --> 00:48:10,700


833
00:48:10,910 --> 00:48:13,200


834
00:48:24,370 --> 00:48:25,910


835
00:48:26,070 --> 00:48:27,950


836
00:48:29,200 --> 00:48:32,370


837
00:48:32,570 --> 00:48:35,160


838
00:48:35,370 --> 00:48:36,530


839
00:48:36,740 --> 00:48:38,530


840
00:48:38,740 --> 00:48:39,910


841
00:48:46,030 --> 00:48:49,990


842
00:48:50,200 --> 00:48:53,780


843
00:48:56,120 --> 00:49:00,490


844
00:49:03,780 --> 00:49:08,070


845
00:49:08,280 --> 00:49:12,030


846
00:49:12,200 --> 00:49:15,780


847
00:49:15,990 --> 00:49:19,570


848
00:49:19,780 --> 00:49:23,820


849
00:49:24,030 --> 00:49:26,570


850
00:49:27,370 --> 00:49:31,660


851
00:49:31,820 --> 00:49:34,620


852
00:49:35,660 --> 00:49:40,780


853
00:49:40,950 --> 00:49:42,410


854
00:49:43,370 --> 00:49:47,990


855
00:49:48,160 --> 00:49:49,320


856
00:49:50,450 --> 00:49:52,320


857
00:49:52,490 --> 00:49:53,820


858
00:49:53,990 --> 00:49:57,410


859
00:49:58,280 --> 00:50:01,700


860
00:50:01,870 --> 00:50:04,410


861
00:50:05,660 --> 00:50:07,200


862
00:50:07,370 --> 00:50:09,320


863
00:50:09,490 --> 00:50:11,950


864
00:50:12,160 --> 00:50:14,200


865
00:50:14,370 --> 00:50:16,200


866
00:50:16,370 --> 00:50:18,320


867
00:50:18,490 --> 00:50:20,870


868
00:50:21,030 --> 00:50:23,490


869
00:50:23,700 --> 00:50:25,410


870
00:50:25,570 --> 00:50:28,200


871
00:50:28,370 --> 00:50:32,820


872
00:50:33,570 --> 00:50:35,870


873
00:50:36,030 --> 00:50:39,280


874
00:50:39,450 --> 00:50:41,370


875
00:50:41,530 --> 00:50:43,490


876
00:50:43,660 --> 00:50:44,700


877
00:50:44,870 --> 00:50:47,990


878
00:50:48,160 --> 00:50:49,950


879
00:50:50,120 --> 00:50:52,990


880
00:50:53,160 --> 00:50:55,070


881
00:50:55,240 --> 00:50:56,910


882
00:50:57,070 --> 00:50:59,910


883
00:51:00,070 --> 00:51:01,950


884
00:51:02,120 --> 00:51:03,450


885
00:51:03,620 --> 00:51:04,910


886
00:51:05,070 --> 00:51:07,030


887
00:51:07,200 --> 00:51:09,320


888
00:51:09,490 --> 00:51:12,450


889
00:51:12,620 --> 00:51:14,700


890
00:51:14,870 --> 00:51:17,620


891
00:51:17,780 --> 00:51:19,370


892
00:51:19,530 --> 00:51:22,200


893
00:51:22,370 --> 00:51:23,700


894
00:51:23,870 --> 00:51:25,410


895
00:51:25,570 --> 00:51:28,990


896
00:51:29,160 --> 00:51:31,160


897
00:51:31,320 --> 00:51:34,160


898
00:51:34,320 --> 00:51:38,070


899
00:51:38,240 --> 00:51:40,870


900
00:51:41,030 --> 00:51:45,200


901
00:51:45,370 --> 00:51:48,780


902
00:51:48,950 --> 00:51:51,620


903
00:51:51,780 --> 00:51:53,200


904
00:51:53,370 --> 00:51:56,280


905
00:51:56,450 --> 00:51:59,990


906
00:52:00,160 --> 00:52:02,450


907
00:52:02,620 --> 00:52:03,660


908
00:52:03,820 --> 00:52:05,820


909
00:52:05,990 --> 00:52:08,780


910
00:52:08,950 --> 00:52:10,570


911
00:52:10,740 --> 00:52:13,620


912
00:52:13,780 --> 00:52:17,820


913
00:52:17,990 --> 00:52:19,620


914
00:52:19,780 --> 00:52:23,160


915
00:52:23,320 --> 00:52:26,030


916
00:52:26,200 --> 00:52:27,990


917
00:52:28,160 --> 00:52:29,990


918
00:52:30,160 --> 00:52:32,490


919
00:52:32,660 --> 00:52:33,990


920
00:52:34,160 --> 00:52:37,530


921
00:52:38,370 --> 00:52:40,870


922
00:52:41,030 --> 00:52:43,620


923
00:52:43,780 --> 00:52:45,450


924
00:52:57,490 --> 00:52:59,530


925
00:52:59,700 --> 00:53:03,370


926
00:53:03,530 --> 00:53:05,120


927
00:53:05,280 --> 00:53:07,820


928
00:53:07,990 --> 00:53:10,950


929
00:53:11,120 --> 00:53:13,530


930
00:53:14,700 --> 00:53:17,700


931
00:53:17,870 --> 00:53:21,120


932
00:53:35,410 --> 00:53:37,700


933
00:53:37,870 --> 00:53:41,530


934
00:53:41,700 --> 00:53:44,240


935
00:53:50,240 --> 00:53:52,660


936
00:53:52,820 --> 00:53:55,240


937
00:53:55,410 --> 00:53:57,490


938
00:53:57,660 --> 00:54:00,240


939
00:54:00,410 --> 00:54:01,950


940
00:54:02,120 --> 00:54:03,280


941
00:54:03,450 --> 00:54:05,030


942
00:54:05,200 --> 00:54:06,910


943
00:54:07,070 --> 00:54:08,410


944
00:54:08,570 --> 00:54:10,780


945
00:54:10,950 --> 00:54:14,070


946
00:54:14,240 --> 00:54:17,700


947
00:54:17,870 --> 00:54:19,910


948
00:54:20,070 --> 00:54:23,990


949
00:54:28,700 --> 00:54:30,950


950
00:54:31,120 --> 00:54:32,700


951
00:54:34,950 --> 00:54:38,490


952
00:54:38,660 --> 00:54:41,030


953
00:54:41,200 --> 00:54:45,410


954
00:54:46,240 --> 00:54:50,870


955
00:54:51,030 --> 00:54:54,370


956
00:54:54,570 --> 00:54:56,530


957
00:54:59,370 --> 00:55:01,660


958
00:55:01,820 --> 00:55:04,490


959
00:55:04,660 --> 00:55:09,070


960
00:55:09,240 --> 00:55:10,910


961
00:55:11,070 --> 00:55:15,030


962
00:55:15,240 --> 00:55:17,740


963
00:55:22,570 --> 00:55:26,620


964
00:55:28,070 --> 00:55:29,490


965
00:55:30,620 --> 00:55:33,780


966
00:55:35,160 --> 00:55:36,990


967
00:55:38,370 --> 00:55:39,910


968
00:55:40,070 --> 00:55:41,990


969
00:55:42,160 --> 00:55:43,950


970
00:55:44,160 --> 00:55:46,030


971
00:55:46,240 --> 00:55:48,990


972
00:55:52,490 --> 00:55:54,070


973
00:55:54,280 --> 00:55:57,740


974
00:55:57,950 --> 00:56:00,160


975
00:56:00,370 --> 00:56:03,200


976
00:56:07,820 --> 00:56:08,820


977
00:56:11,570 --> 00:56:13,570


978
00:56:14,490 --> 00:56:16,780


979
00:56:16,990 --> 00:56:17,990


980
00:56:18,200 --> 00:56:20,700


981
00:56:24,450 --> 00:56:26,700


982
00:56:27,280 --> 00:56:28,280


983
00:56:28,490 --> 00:56:31,410


984
00:56:31,620 --> 00:56:33,240


985
00:56:33,410 --> 00:56:34,410


986
00:56:34,620 --> 00:56:38,200


987
00:56:38,410 --> 00:56:40,120


988
00:56:40,320 --> 00:56:41,410


989
00:56:41,620 --> 00:56:44,780


990
00:56:44,990 --> 00:56:50,660


991
00:56:50,820 --> 00:56:52,990


992
00:56:53,200 --> 00:56:55,950


993
00:56:56,160 --> 00:56:59,990


994
00:57:00,200 --> 00:57:01,370


995
00:57:01,570 --> 00:57:04,950


996
00:57:05,160 --> 00:57:07,160


997
00:57:07,370 --> 00:57:09,160


998
00:57:09,370 --> 00:57:12,620


999
00:57:12,820 --> 00:57:14,200


1000
00:57:14,370 --> 00:57:17,120


1001
00:57:17,280 --> 00:57:20,280


1002
00:57:20,490 --> 00:57:23,160


1003
00:57:23,320 --> 00:57:25,660


1004
00:57:25,870 --> 00:57:27,990


1005
00:57:28,160 --> 00:57:30,660


1006
00:57:30,870 --> 00:57:32,570


1007
00:57:32,780 --> 00:57:36,280


1008
00:57:36,490 --> 00:57:38,820


1009
00:57:39,030 --> 00:57:42,030


1010
00:57:42,200 --> 00:57:45,950


1011
00:57:46,160 --> 00:57:48,990


1012
00:57:49,200 --> 00:57:52,910


1013
00:57:54,320 --> 00:57:56,860


1014
00:57:57,070 --> 00:57:59,200


1015
00:58:07,160 --> 00:58:12,110


1016
00:58:14,280 --> 00:58:16,410


1017
00:58:16,610 --> 00:58:21,660


1018
00:58:22,570 --> 00:58:25,240


1019
00:58:25,410 --> 00:58:29,240


1020
00:58:29,860 --> 00:58:34,160


1021
00:58:34,320 --> 00:58:36,530


1022
00:58:36,700 --> 00:58:38,410


1023
00:58:41,700 --> 00:58:44,240


1024
00:58:48,660 --> 00:58:50,030


1025
00:58:50,240 --> 00:58:53,240


1026
00:58:59,860 --> 00:59:02,950


1027
00:59:03,110 --> 00:59:06,360


1028
00:59:06,570 --> 00:59:09,410


1029
00:59:09,570 --> 00:59:12,570


1030
00:59:12,740 --> 00:59:16,160


1031
00:59:16,320 --> 00:59:18,280


1032
00:59:19,240 --> 00:59:22,030


1033
00:59:22,200 --> 00:59:25,780


1034
00:59:25,950 --> 00:59:29,110


1035
00:59:29,280 --> 00:59:31,660


1036
00:59:33,160 --> 00:59:35,280


1037
00:59:35,950 --> 00:59:41,660


1038
00:59:42,450 --> 00:59:48,070


1039
00:59:48,240 --> 00:59:51,410


1040
00:59:55,240 --> 00:59:59,780


1041
01:00:09,030 --> 01:00:10,990


1042
01:00:12,280 --> 01:00:14,490


1043
01:00:14,660 --> 01:00:16,530


1044
01:00:18,200 --> 01:00:20,280


1045
01:00:21,610 --> 01:00:23,490


1046
01:00:23,660 --> 01:00:25,110


1047
01:00:25,280 --> 01:00:28,780


1048
01:00:28,950 --> 01:00:34,860


1049
01:00:35,030 --> 01:00:41,110


1050
01:00:41,280 --> 01:00:44,320


1051
01:00:53,070 --> 01:00:55,530


1052
01:00:55,700 --> 01:00:57,240


1053
01:00:57,410 --> 01:00:59,700


1054
01:00:59,860 --> 01:01:03,070


1055
01:01:03,240 --> 01:01:05,410


1056
01:01:05,570 --> 01:01:07,070


1057
01:01:07,240 --> 01:01:10,160


1058
01:01:11,860 --> 01:01:15,700


1059
01:01:16,410 --> 01:01:18,200


1060
01:01:18,360 --> 01:01:19,610


1061
01:01:19,820 --> 01:01:20,820


1062
01:01:21,030 --> 01:01:24,820


1063
01:01:24,990 --> 01:01:29,070


1064
01:01:29,240 --> 01:01:30,740


1065
01:01:30,910 --> 01:01:33,410


1066
01:01:33,570 --> 01:01:35,110


1067
01:01:35,280 --> 01:01:37,030


1068
01:01:37,200 --> 01:01:39,570


1069
01:01:39,740 --> 01:01:42,320


1070
01:01:42,490 --> 01:01:44,950


1071
01:01:45,110 --> 01:01:47,200


1072
01:01:47,360 --> 01:01:49,160


1073
01:01:49,320 --> 01:01:53,700


1074
01:01:53,860 --> 01:01:56,490


1075
01:01:56,660 --> 01:01:58,570


1076
01:01:58,740 --> 01:02:03,450


1077
01:02:03,610 --> 01:02:07,490


1078
01:02:08,410 --> 01:02:10,450


1079
01:02:10,610 --> 01:02:15,950


1080
01:02:16,110 --> 01:02:18,660


1081
01:02:18,860 --> 01:02:21,530


1082
01:02:22,530 --> 01:02:23,660


1083
01:02:23,820 --> 01:02:26,410


1084
01:02:26,570 --> 01:02:28,820


1085
01:02:28,990 --> 01:02:32,570


1086
01:02:32,740 --> 01:02:33,910


1087
01:02:34,070 --> 01:02:36,280


1088
01:02:36,450 --> 01:02:39,780


1089
01:02:39,950 --> 01:02:42,530


1090
01:02:42,700 --> 01:02:45,910


1091
01:02:46,070 --> 01:02:47,820


1092
01:02:47,990 --> 01:02:49,780


1093
01:02:49,950 --> 01:02:51,110


1094
01:02:51,280 --> 01:02:54,280


1095
01:02:54,450 --> 01:02:58,910


1096
01:02:59,070 --> 01:03:01,700


1097
01:03:01,860 --> 01:03:04,410


1098
01:03:04,570 --> 01:03:06,530


1099
01:03:06,700 --> 01:03:08,820


1100
01:03:08,990 --> 01:03:10,570


1101
01:03:10,740 --> 01:03:12,780


1102
01:03:12,950 --> 01:03:14,610


1103
01:03:14,780 --> 01:03:16,530


1104
01:03:16,700 --> 01:03:20,240


1105
01:03:21,990 --> 01:03:25,070


1106
01:03:25,240 --> 01:03:28,070


1107
01:03:28,240 --> 01:03:30,160


1108
01:03:30,320 --> 01:03:31,860


1109
01:03:32,030 --> 01:03:34,700


1110
01:03:34,860 --> 01:03:36,820


1111
01:03:36,990 --> 01:03:39,990


1112
01:03:40,160 --> 01:03:42,950


1113
01:03:43,110 --> 01:03:45,950


1114
01:03:46,110 --> 01:03:49,240


1115
01:03:49,410 --> 01:03:52,450


1116
01:03:55,200 --> 01:03:58,950


1117
01:03:59,450 --> 01:04:03,410


1118
01:04:20,820 --> 01:04:23,320


1119
01:04:23,490 --> 01:04:25,200


1120
01:04:25,360 --> 01:04:26,860


1121
01:04:27,030 --> 01:04:29,490


1122
01:04:29,660 --> 01:04:31,490


1123
01:04:31,660 --> 01:04:34,490


1124
01:04:34,660 --> 01:04:38,610


1125
01:04:38,780 --> 01:04:40,860


1126
01:04:41,030 --> 01:04:45,660


1127
01:04:45,820 --> 01:04:47,740


1128
01:04:47,910 --> 01:04:49,110


1129
01:04:49,280 --> 01:04:51,490


1130
01:04:53,780 --> 01:04:55,660


1131
01:04:55,820 --> 01:04:56,990


1132
01:04:57,160 --> 01:04:58,610


1133
01:04:58,780 --> 01:05:01,030


1134
01:05:01,200 --> 01:05:02,660


1135
01:05:13,910 --> 01:05:15,030


1136
01:05:15,200 --> 01:05:17,450


1137
01:05:17,610 --> 01:05:18,780


1138
01:05:18,950 --> 01:05:20,910


1139
01:05:21,070 --> 01:05:23,200


1140
01:05:23,360 --> 01:05:26,320


1141
01:05:26,490 --> 01:05:28,280


1142
01:05:28,450 --> 01:05:29,860


1143
01:05:30,030 --> 01:05:32,070


1144
01:05:32,240 --> 01:05:34,320


1145
01:05:34,910 --> 01:05:36,410


1146
01:05:36,570 --> 01:05:39,200


1147
01:05:39,360 --> 01:05:41,410


1148
01:05:41,570 --> 01:05:42,610


1149
01:05:42,780 --> 01:05:44,910


1150
01:05:45,660 --> 01:05:46,820


1151
01:05:46,990 --> 01:05:49,530


1152
01:05:49,700 --> 01:05:53,030


1153
01:05:53,200 --> 01:05:54,950


1154
01:05:55,740 --> 01:05:57,280


1155
01:05:57,450 --> 01:05:59,530


1156
01:06:00,360 --> 01:06:02,410


1157
01:06:02,570 --> 01:06:04,160


1158
01:06:04,320 --> 01:06:06,660


1159
01:06:06,820 --> 01:06:09,660


1160
01:06:09,820 --> 01:06:13,030


1161
01:06:13,200 --> 01:06:14,450


1162
01:06:14,610 --> 01:06:17,320


1163
01:06:17,490 --> 01:06:19,610


1164
01:06:20,530 --> 01:06:23,320


1165
01:06:23,490 --> 01:06:27,910


1166
01:06:28,070 --> 01:06:30,030


1167
01:06:30,200 --> 01:06:33,360


1168
01:06:34,030 --> 01:06:35,450


1169
01:06:36,610 --> 01:06:38,610


1170
01:06:38,780 --> 01:06:40,700


1171
01:06:40,860 --> 01:06:44,610


1172
01:06:46,780 --> 01:06:49,320


1173
01:06:49,490 --> 01:06:51,950


1174
01:06:54,410 --> 01:06:56,360


1175
01:07:02,990 --> 01:07:04,990


1176
01:07:06,990 --> 01:07:09,910


1177
01:07:25,450 --> 01:07:28,490


1178
01:07:28,660 --> 01:07:31,280


1179
01:07:31,450 --> 01:07:33,860


1180
01:07:37,110 --> 01:07:39,280


1181
01:07:41,910 --> 01:07:44,070


1182
01:07:45,200 --> 01:07:47,660


1183
01:07:47,820 --> 01:07:51,070


1184
01:07:51,240 --> 01:07:54,280


1185
01:07:54,450 --> 01:07:56,860


1186
01:07:57,030 --> 01:08:00,070


1187
01:08:00,240 --> 01:08:03,200


1188
01:08:03,360 --> 01:08:05,530


1189
01:08:06,360 --> 01:08:09,490


1190
01:08:09,660 --> 01:08:13,280


1191
01:08:13,450 --> 01:08:17,740


1192
01:08:17,910 --> 01:08:19,780


1193
01:08:19,950 --> 01:08:21,490


1194
01:08:21,660 --> 01:08:23,160


1195
01:08:23,320 --> 01:08:24,990


1196
01:08:25,160 --> 01:08:29,410


1197
01:08:29,570 --> 01:08:31,700


1198
01:08:32,110 --> 01:08:34,820


1199
01:08:34,990 --> 01:08:37,240


1200
01:08:37,410 --> 01:08:40,030


1201
01:08:41,530 --> 01:08:43,450


1202
01:08:52,030 --> 01:08:53,070


1203
01:08:53,950 --> 01:08:55,570


1204
01:08:55,740 --> 01:08:58,450


1205
01:08:58,610 --> 01:09:00,450


1206
01:09:00,610 --> 01:09:02,160


1207
01:09:02,320 --> 01:09:05,160


1208
01:09:05,320 --> 01:09:07,780


1209
01:09:07,950 --> 01:09:09,990


1210
01:09:10,160 --> 01:09:12,780


1211
01:09:12,950 --> 01:09:15,490


1212
01:09:15,660 --> 01:09:17,990


1213
01:09:18,160 --> 01:09:20,200


1214
01:09:20,360 --> 01:09:22,740


1215
01:09:26,280 --> 01:09:28,360


1216
01:09:28,530 --> 01:09:31,490


1217
01:09:31,660 --> 01:09:34,410


1218
01:09:34,570 --> 01:09:37,570


1219
01:09:37,740 --> 01:09:41,240


1220
01:09:41,410 --> 01:09:43,490


1221
01:09:44,240 --> 01:09:46,280


1222
01:09:46,450 --> 01:09:50,280


1223
01:09:51,820 --> 01:09:53,740


1224
01:09:53,910 --> 01:09:58,570


1225
01:10:00,660 --> 01:10:02,990


1226
01:10:11,280 --> 01:10:14,490


1227
01:10:14,700 --> 01:10:17,700


1228
01:10:18,740 --> 01:10:21,610


1229
01:10:21,780 --> 01:10:23,740


1230
01:10:23,910 --> 01:10:26,030


1231
01:10:27,280 --> 01:10:29,610


1232
01:10:29,780 --> 01:10:33,780


1233
01:10:33,950 --> 01:10:36,160


1234
01:10:36,320 --> 01:10:37,820


1235
01:10:40,530 --> 01:10:43,110


1236
01:10:43,280 --> 01:10:45,360


1237
01:10:45,530 --> 01:10:47,320


1238
01:10:49,240 --> 01:10:51,950


1239
01:10:58,860 --> 01:11:00,950


1240
01:11:01,110 --> 01:11:04,280


1241
01:11:04,450 --> 01:11:08,110


1242
01:11:08,280 --> 01:11:10,950


1243
01:11:11,110 --> 01:11:13,860


1244
01:11:14,030 --> 01:11:15,490


1245
01:11:15,660 --> 01:11:18,570


1246
01:11:18,740 --> 01:11:23,660


1247
01:11:23,820 --> 01:11:26,320


1248
01:11:26,490 --> 01:11:29,110


1249
01:11:29,280 --> 01:11:31,110


1250
01:11:31,280 --> 01:11:34,610


1251
01:11:34,780 --> 01:11:38,450


1252
01:11:38,610 --> 01:11:40,910


1253
01:11:41,070 --> 01:11:44,990


1254
01:11:45,160 --> 01:11:47,490


1255
01:11:47,660 --> 01:11:48,950


1256
01:11:49,110 --> 01:11:51,780


1257
01:12:01,160 --> 01:12:03,910


1258
01:12:04,070 --> 01:12:05,410


1259
01:12:06,990 --> 01:12:10,110


1260
01:12:13,450 --> 01:12:15,820


1261
01:12:17,240 --> 01:12:18,610


1262
01:12:18,780 --> 01:12:20,700


1263
01:12:20,860 --> 01:12:22,740


1264
01:12:24,860 --> 01:12:27,200


1265
01:12:27,360 --> 01:12:29,610


1266
01:12:30,280 --> 01:12:33,570


1267
01:12:33,740 --> 01:12:37,490


1268
01:12:41,410 --> 01:12:44,240


1269
01:12:46,990 --> 01:12:48,660


1270
01:13:12,950 --> 01:13:15,820


1271
01:13:15,990 --> 01:13:19,360


1272
01:13:19,530 --> 01:13:22,570


1273
01:13:22,740 --> 01:13:25,030


1274
01:13:25,200 --> 01:13:27,070


1275
01:13:29,450 --> 01:13:34,360


1276
01:13:35,740 --> 01:13:39,070


1277
01:13:43,740 --> 01:13:45,740


1278
01:13:45,910 --> 01:13:48,780


1279
01:13:48,950 --> 01:13:51,200


1280
01:13:51,360 --> 01:13:54,240


1281
01:13:56,950 --> 01:13:59,660


1282
01:13:59,820 --> 01:14:02,820


1283
01:14:02,990 --> 01:14:06,110


1284
01:14:07,200 --> 01:14:08,990


1285
01:14:10,410 --> 01:14:12,570


1286
01:14:25,030 --> 01:14:27,280


1287
01:14:27,450 --> 01:14:30,280


1288
01:14:30,450 --> 01:14:33,570


1289
01:14:35,030 --> 01:14:37,780


1290
01:14:37,950 --> 01:14:39,110


1291
01:14:39,280 --> 01:14:41,490


1292
01:14:41,660 --> 01:14:43,740


1293
01:14:43,910 --> 01:14:48,070


1294
01:14:48,240 --> 01:14:49,740


1295
01:14:49,910 --> 01:14:51,990


1296
01:14:52,160 --> 01:14:54,070


1297
01:14:54,240 --> 01:14:57,570


1298
01:14:57,740 --> 01:14:59,530


1299
01:14:59,700 --> 01:15:01,660


1300
01:15:01,820 --> 01:15:04,740


1301
01:15:04,910 --> 01:15:06,570


1302
01:15:08,280 --> 01:15:09,700


1303
01:15:09,860 --> 01:15:11,360


1304
01:15:11,530 --> 01:15:15,570


1305
01:15:17,400 --> 01:15:18,950


1306
01:15:19,110 --> 01:15:22,530


1307
01:15:22,700 --> 01:15:25,450


1308
01:15:25,610 --> 01:15:27,820


1309
01:15:28,650 --> 01:15:31,780


1310
01:15:31,950 --> 01:15:33,490


1311
01:15:33,650 --> 01:15:37,450


1312
01:15:37,610 --> 01:15:39,150


1313
01:15:39,320 --> 01:15:41,740


1314
01:15:41,900 --> 01:15:44,650


1315
01:15:44,820 --> 01:15:46,240


1316
01:15:46,400 --> 01:15:48,490


1317
01:15:48,650 --> 01:15:50,860


1318
01:15:51,030 --> 01:15:55,610


1319
01:15:55,780 --> 01:15:58,360


1320
01:16:03,400 --> 01:16:06,860


1321
01:16:22,490 --> 01:16:23,780


1322
01:16:31,070 --> 01:16:32,650


1323
01:16:32,820 --> 01:16:34,110


1324
01:16:34,280 --> 01:16:35,860


1325
01:16:36,030 --> 01:16:38,320


1326
01:16:38,490 --> 01:16:41,450


1327
01:16:41,610 --> 01:16:45,700


1328
01:16:45,860 --> 01:16:46,900


1329
01:16:47,070 --> 01:16:48,530


1330
01:16:48,700 --> 01:16:51,070


1331
01:16:51,240 --> 01:16:54,320


1332
01:16:54,490 --> 01:16:57,990


1333
01:17:01,110 --> 01:17:04,950


1334
01:17:05,150 --> 01:17:07,650


1335
01:17:08,320 --> 01:17:09,780


1336
01:17:09,950 --> 01:17:12,490


1337
01:17:14,110 --> 01:17:15,700


1338
01:17:17,240 --> 01:17:22,740


1339
01:17:22,900 --> 01:17:24,610


1340
01:17:24,820 --> 01:17:26,280


1341
01:17:26,490 --> 01:17:29,450


1342
01:17:29,650 --> 01:17:31,530


1343
01:17:31,740 --> 01:17:36,530


1344
01:17:37,490 --> 01:17:38,530


1345
01:17:45,740 --> 01:17:47,700


1346
01:17:47,900 --> 01:17:51,950


1347
01:17:52,150 --> 01:17:54,280


1348
01:17:54,490 --> 01:17:56,650


1349
01:18:09,570 --> 01:18:10,990


1350
01:18:12,650 --> 01:18:16,610


1351
01:18:20,650 --> 01:18:22,860


1352
01:18:23,070 --> 01:18:24,530


1353
01:18:24,700 --> 01:18:28,360


1354
01:18:28,570 --> 01:18:31,070


1355
01:18:31,280 --> 01:18:34,150


1356
01:18:36,280 --> 01:18:37,490


1357
01:18:37,700 --> 01:18:39,240


1358
01:18:39,450 --> 01:18:44,150


1359
01:18:59,820 --> 01:19:03,150


1360
01:19:03,320 --> 01:19:07,070


1361
01:19:07,280 --> 01:19:10,450


1362
01:19:10,610 --> 01:19:13,360


1363
01:19:13,570 --> 01:19:16,570


1364
01:19:19,610 --> 01:19:22,780


1365
01:19:22,990 --> 01:19:26,610


1366
01:19:26,820 --> 01:19:30,400


1367
01:19:30,610 --> 01:19:34,030


1368
01:19:34,240 --> 01:19:37,570


1369
01:19:37,780 --> 01:19:41,360


1370
01:19:41,570 --> 01:19:45,780


1371
01:19:58,400 --> 01:20:00,280


1372
01:20:19,450 --> 01:20:22,110


1373
01:20:23,820 --> 01:20:26,200


1374
01:20:26,360 --> 01:20:28,240


1375
01:20:29,030 --> 01:20:31,240


1376
01:20:31,400 --> 01:20:34,320


1377
01:20:34,490 --> 01:20:39,030


1378
01:20:39,240 --> 01:20:42,070


1379
01:20:42,280 --> 01:20:45,110


1380
01:20:45,320 --> 01:20:47,200


1381
01:20:47,400 --> 01:20:49,200


1382
01:20:49,400 --> 01:20:52,650


1383
01:20:52,820 --> 01:20:55,200


1384
01:20:55,400 --> 01:20:57,030


1385
01:20:57,240 --> 01:20:58,650


1386
01:20:58,820 --> 01:21:00,860


1387
01:21:01,990 --> 01:21:04,990


1388
01:21:05,150 --> 01:21:08,240


1389
01:21:08,450 --> 01:21:09,530


1390
01:21:09,700 --> 01:21:11,150


1391
01:21:11,320 --> 01:21:13,990


1392
01:21:14,150 --> 01:21:15,950


1393
01:21:16,110 --> 01:21:18,650


1394
01:21:18,820 --> 01:21:20,280


1395
01:21:20,450 --> 01:21:22,650


1396
01:21:22,860 --> 01:21:26,280


1397
01:21:26,450 --> 01:21:28,740


1398
01:21:29,900 --> 01:21:33,320


1399
01:21:37,570 --> 01:21:39,280


1400
01:21:40,070 --> 01:21:42,360


1401
01:22:03,030 --> 01:22:04,700


1402
01:22:56,070 --> 01:22:57,990


1403
01:22:58,150 --> 01:23:00,900


1404
01:23:01,070 --> 01:23:03,150


1405
01:23:05,530 --> 01:23:06,950


1406
01:23:07,110 --> 01:23:08,780


1407
01:23:11,200 --> 01:23:12,360


1408
01:23:14,990 --> 01:23:16,820


1409
01:23:16,990 --> 01:23:18,400


1410
01:23:18,570 --> 01:23:20,320


1411
01:23:20,490 --> 01:23:22,950


1412
01:23:23,150 --> 01:23:26,070


1413
01:23:26,240 --> 01:23:29,400


1414
01:23:29,570 --> 01:23:34,110


1415
01:23:34,280 --> 01:23:35,610


1416
01:23:35,780 --> 01:23:39,110


1417
01:23:39,280 --> 01:23:41,150


1418
01:23:46,320 --> 01:23:48,320


1419
01:23:49,280 --> 01:23:50,700


1420
01:23:50,860 --> 01:23:54,280


1421
01:23:54,450 --> 01:23:55,610


1422
01:23:55,780 --> 01:23:58,150


1423
01:23:58,320 --> 01:24:00,110


1424
01:24:00,280 --> 01:24:02,240


1425
01:24:02,400 --> 01:24:04,360


1426
01:24:04,530 --> 01:24:07,200


1427
01:24:07,360 --> 01:24:09,530


1428
01:24:09,700 --> 01:24:10,780


1429
01:24:10,950 --> 01:24:12,530


1430
01:24:12,700 --> 01:24:15,450


1431
01:24:15,610 --> 01:24:18,030


1432
01:24:18,200 --> 01:24:19,900


1433
01:24:20,070 --> 01:24:21,820


1434
01:24:21,990 --> 01:24:24,070


1435
01:24:24,240 --> 01:24:26,280


1436
01:24:26,450 --> 01:24:27,900


1437
01:24:28,070 --> 01:24:31,400


1438
01:24:32,400 --> 01:24:34,490


1439
01:24:34,650 --> 01:24:37,280


1440
01:24:41,740 --> 01:24:43,490


1441
01:24:45,280 --> 01:24:49,030


1442
01:24:49,700 --> 01:24:51,240


1443
01:24:51,400 --> 01:24:53,530


1444
01:24:53,700 --> 01:24:56,070


1445
01:24:56,240 --> 01:24:57,740


1446
01:24:57,900 --> 01:24:59,900


1447
01:25:00,070 --> 01:25:01,950


1448
01:25:02,110 --> 01:25:04,530


1449
01:25:04,700 --> 01:25:06,030


1450
01:25:06,200 --> 01:25:08,900


1451
01:25:11,110 --> 01:25:13,360


1452
01:25:13,530 --> 01:25:15,950


1453
01:25:16,900 --> 01:25:18,900


1454
01:25:19,070 --> 01:25:21,200


1455
01:25:21,360 --> 01:25:23,570


1456
01:25:24,650 --> 01:25:26,780


1457
01:25:26,950 --> 01:25:28,700


1458
01:25:28,860 --> 01:25:30,820


1459
01:25:30,990 --> 01:25:32,650


1460
01:25:32,820 --> 01:25:34,860


1461
01:25:35,030 --> 01:25:37,240


1462
01:25:37,400 --> 01:25:39,740


1463
01:25:39,900 --> 01:25:43,990


1464
01:25:44,150 --> 01:25:46,780


1465
01:25:46,950 --> 01:25:48,320


1466
01:25:48,490 --> 01:25:51,400


1467
01:25:56,110 --> 01:25:59,820


1468
01:25:59,990 --> 01:26:03,240


1469
01:26:03,400 --> 01:26:06,570


1470
01:26:06,740 --> 01:26:09,110


1471
01:26:17,570 --> 01:26:18,950


1472
01:26:19,700 --> 01:26:21,150


1473
01:26:21,320 --> 01:26:23,450


1474
01:26:23,610 --> 01:26:25,030


1475
01:26:25,200 --> 01:26:27,700


1476
01:26:28,780 --> 01:26:31,400


1477
01:26:31,570 --> 01:26:34,070


1478
01:26:34,240 --> 01:26:35,320


1479
01:26:35,490 --> 01:26:37,900


1480
01:26:38,070 --> 01:26:39,950


1481
01:26:47,400 --> 01:26:48,780


1482
01:26:48,950 --> 01:26:51,700


1483
01:26:51,860 --> 01:26:53,110


1484
01:26:53,280 --> 01:26:55,780


1485
01:26:57,320 --> 01:26:58,360


1486
01:26:58,530 --> 01:27:00,200


1487
01:27:00,360 --> 01:27:02,780


1488
01:27:02,950 --> 01:27:05,070


1489
01:27:05,240 --> 01:27:07,200


1490
01:27:07,360 --> 01:27:10,860


1491
01:27:16,490 --> 01:27:19,530


1492
01:27:19,700 --> 01:27:21,490


1493
01:27:21,650 --> 01:27:26,150


1494
01:27:26,320 --> 01:27:29,320


1495
01:27:29,490 --> 01:27:31,400


1496
01:27:31,570 --> 01:27:33,280


1497
01:27:33,450 --> 01:27:34,950


1498
01:27:35,110 --> 01:27:38,150


1499
01:27:38,320 --> 01:27:40,200


1500
01:27:40,360 --> 01:27:42,360


1501
01:27:42,530 --> 01:27:45,950


1502
01:27:46,110 --> 01:27:48,740


1503
01:27:49,740 --> 01:27:51,900


1504
01:27:52,070 --> 01:27:55,950


1505
01:27:57,320 --> 01:27:59,320


1506
01:27:59,490 --> 01:28:00,900


1507
01:28:01,070 --> 01:28:03,360


1508
01:28:03,530 --> 01:28:05,110


1509
01:28:05,280 --> 01:28:08,570


1510
01:28:08,740 --> 01:28:09,950


1511
01:28:10,110 --> 01:28:13,240


1512
01:28:14,700 --> 01:28:16,530


1513
01:28:16,700 --> 01:28:18,030


1514
01:28:18,200 --> 01:28:20,280


1515
01:28:20,450 --> 01:28:21,570


1516
01:28:28,740 --> 01:28:31,030


1517
01:28:31,200 --> 01:28:33,860


1518
01:28:34,030 --> 01:28:37,240


1519
01:28:37,400 --> 01:28:39,240


1520
01:28:39,400 --> 01:28:42,490


1521
01:28:42,650 --> 01:28:45,650


1522
01:28:46,530 --> 01:28:47,860


1523
01:28:52,150 --> 01:28:54,360


1524
01:28:54,530 --> 01:28:56,950


1525
01:28:57,110 --> 01:28:58,400


1526
01:28:58,570 --> 01:28:59,990


1527
01:29:00,150 --> 01:29:02,900


1528
01:29:03,610 --> 01:29:05,030


1529
01:29:05,200 --> 01:29:07,490


1530
01:29:07,650 --> 01:29:08,780


1531
01:29:08,950 --> 01:29:14,070


1532
01:29:14,240 --> 01:29:17,360


1533
01:29:17,530 --> 01:29:19,740


1534
01:29:19,900 --> 01:29:22,150


1535
01:29:22,320 --> 01:29:23,530


1536
01:29:23,700 --> 01:29:25,780


1537
01:29:26,450 --> 01:29:28,610


1538
01:29:28,780 --> 01:29:31,110


1539
01:29:32,400 --> 01:29:33,900


1540
01:29:34,070 --> 01:29:35,740


1541
01:29:35,900 --> 01:29:37,240


1542
01:29:37,400 --> 01:29:40,320


1543
01:29:40,490 --> 01:29:42,900


1544
01:29:43,070 --> 01:29:45,530


1545
01:29:45,700 --> 01:29:49,700


1546
01:29:49,860 --> 01:29:52,400


1547
01:29:52,570 --> 01:29:56,240


1548
01:29:56,400 --> 01:29:57,860


1549
01:29:58,030 --> 01:30:00,400


1550
01:30:00,570 --> 01:30:01,820


1551
01:30:01,990 --> 01:30:03,740


1552
01:30:03,900 --> 01:30:06,280


1553
01:30:06,450 --> 01:30:09,030


1554
01:30:09,200 --> 01:30:12,200


1555
01:30:12,360 --> 01:30:14,530


1556
01:30:15,820 --> 01:30:19,200


1557
01:30:19,360 --> 01:30:23,490


1558
01:30:23,650 --> 01:30:25,530


1559
01:30:25,700 --> 01:30:28,950


1560
01:30:43,320 --> 01:30:44,740


1561
01:30:44,900 --> 01:30:46,780


1562
01:30:53,240 --> 01:30:55,740


1563
01:30:55,900 --> 01:30:59,950


1564
01:31:00,110 --> 01:31:01,860


1565
01:31:02,030 --> 01:31:04,280


1566
01:31:04,450 --> 01:31:06,490


1567
01:31:06,650 --> 01:31:08,610


1568
01:31:32,400 --> 01:31:34,990


1569
01:31:35,150 --> 01:31:37,990


1570
01:31:38,070 --> 01:31:39,030


1571
01:31:39,110 --> 01:31:41,240


1572
01:31:41,400 --> 01:31:42,820


1573
01:31:43,360 --> 01:31:45,820


1574
01:31:45,990 --> 01:31:48,860


1575
01:31:50,990 --> 01:31:52,860


1576
01:32:05,360 --> 01:32:08,650


1577
01:32:08,820 --> 01:32:11,820


1578
01:32:11,990 --> 01:32:14,610


1579
01:32:14,780 --> 01:32:18,360


1580
01:32:18,530 --> 01:32:21,070


1581
01:32:28,780 --> 01:32:31,240


1582
01:32:31,400 --> 01:32:35,110


1583
01:32:35,280 --> 01:32:38,990


1584
01:32:39,150 --> 01:32:41,360


1585
01:32:43,900 --> 01:32:46,360


1586
01:32:46,530 --> 01:32:48,280


1587
01:32:48,440 --> 01:32:51,110


1588
01:32:51,280 --> 01:32:53,280


1589
01:32:54,070 --> 01:32:55,820


1590
01:32:55,990 --> 01:32:57,990


1591
01:32:58,150 --> 01:33:01,780


1592
01:33:01,940 --> 01:33:06,820


1593
01:33:06,990 --> 01:33:09,320


1594
01:33:09,490 --> 01:33:12,110


1595
01:33:12,280 --> 01:33:14,940


1596
01:33:15,110 --> 01:33:18,030


1597
01:33:18,190 --> 01:33:20,110


1598
01:33:20,280 --> 01:33:21,990


1599
01:33:22,150 --> 01:33:24,030


1600
01:33:24,190 --> 01:33:28,860


1601
01:33:31,030 --> 01:33:33,860


1602
01:33:34,030 --> 01:33:36,610


1603
01:33:36,780 --> 01:33:39,990


1604
01:33:40,150 --> 01:33:42,400


1605
01:33:42,570 --> 01:33:45,070


1606
01:33:45,240 --> 01:33:48,940


1607
01:33:49,110 --> 01:33:52,030


1608
01:33:52,190 --> 01:33:54,860


1609
01:33:57,740 --> 01:34:00,440


1610
01:34:00,610 --> 01:34:04,240


1611
01:34:04,400 --> 01:34:06,610


1612
01:34:06,780 --> 01:34:09,030


1613
01:34:09,190 --> 01:34:10,650


1614
01:34:10,820 --> 01:34:14,280


1615
01:34:14,440 --> 01:34:17,490


1616
01:34:22,280 --> 01:34:27,360


1617
01:34:27,530 --> 01:34:29,610


1618
01:34:29,780 --> 01:34:31,400


1619
01:34:33,490 --> 01:34:36,150


1620
01:34:36,320 --> 01:34:38,110


1621
01:34:38,280 --> 01:34:40,190


1622
01:34:42,070 --> 01:34:44,320


1623
01:34:47,650 --> 01:34:49,440


1624
01:34:55,610 --> 01:34:57,280


1625
01:34:57,780 --> 01:35:00,150


1626
01:35:04,360 --> 01:35:06,820


1627
01:35:06,990 --> 01:35:08,110


1628
01:35:08,280 --> 01:35:10,860


1629
01:35:11,650 --> 01:35:13,280


1630
01:35:17,030 --> 01:35:20,440


1631
01:35:24,990 --> 01:35:27,240


1632
01:35:27,400 --> 01:35:29,030


1633
01:35:34,990 --> 01:35:36,190


1634
01:35:36,360 --> 01:35:38,900


1635
01:36:03,990 --> 01:36:05,780


1636
01:36:10,690 --> 01:36:14,360


1637
01:36:17,030 --> 01:36:20,610


1638
01:36:20,780 --> 01:36:23,650


1639
01:36:43,440 --> 01:36:45,610


1640
01:36:45,780 --> 01:36:48,490


1641
01:36:48,650 --> 01:36:50,990


1642
01:40:11,690 --> 01:40:14,150


1643
01:40:14,360 --> 01:40:15,740


1644
01:40:16,900 --> 01:40:19,990


1645
01:40:20,190 --> 01:40:22,650


1646
01:40:24,150 --> 01:40:25,900


1647
01:40:26,110 --> 01:40:29,030


1648
01:40:29,240 --> 01:40:32,320


1649
01:40:32,530 --> 01:40:34,320


1650
01:40:34,490 --> 01:40:37,490


1651
01:40:37,690 --> 01:40:41,400


1652
01:40:42,190 --> 01:40:43,440


1653
01:40:43,650 --> 01:40:45,860


1654
01:40:46,070 --> 01:40:50,190


1655
01:40:50,360 --> 01:40:53,190


1656
01:40:56,070 --> 01:40:59,150


1657
01:40:59,320 --> 01:41:03,070


1658
01:41:03,280 --> 01:41:06,360


1659
01:41:06,530 --> 01:41:07,820


1660
01:41:08,030 --> 01:41:11,610


1661
01:41:11,820 --> 01:41:14,740


1662
01:41:14,900 --> 01:41:17,110


1663
01:41:17,320 --> 01:41:21,690


1664
01:41:21,900 --> 01:41:23,440


1665
01:41:23,650 --> 01:41:26,900


1666
01:41:29,150 --> 01:41:31,820


1667
01:41:32,030 --> 01:41:34,940


1668
01:41:37,070 --> 01:41:38,860


1669
01:41:39,030 --> 01:41:40,740


1670
01:41:40,940 --> 01:41:42,900


1671
01:41:43,110 --> 01:41:44,360


1672
01:41:44,570 --> 01:41:45,940


1673
01:41:46,150 --> 01:41:48,280


1674
01:41:48,440 --> 01:41:49,990


1675
01:41:51,440 --> 01:41:53,240


1676
01:41:54,280 --> 01:41:55,280


1677
01:41:58,400 --> 01:42:00,110


1678
01:42:00,320 --> 01:42:02,280


1679
01:42:02,440 --> 01:42:04,240


1680
01:42:05,280 --> 01:42:07,940


1681
01:42:08,110 --> 01:42:10,320


1682
01:42:10,530 --> 01:42:13,780


1683
01:42:13,940 --> 01:42:16,320


1684
01:42:16,530 --> 01:42:18,400


1685
01:42:39,190 --> 01:42:41,150


1686
01:42:43,990 --> 01:42:46,190


1687
01:42:47,610 --> 01:42:50,610


1688
01:42:51,610 --> 01:42:53,150


1689
01:42:53,320 --> 01:42:55,190


1690
01:42:55,400 --> 01:42:56,570


1691
01:42:58,240 --> 01:42:59,940


1692
01:43:02,740 --> 01:43:04,280


1693
01:43:05,360 --> 01:43:06,900


1694
01:43:07,110 --> 01:43:08,740


1695
01:43:08,900 --> 01:43:10,240


1696
01:43:12,190 --> 01:43:14,570


1697
01:43:14,740 --> 01:43:16,360


1698
01:43:16,530 --> 01:43:18,900


1699
01:43:19,110 --> 01:43:20,650


1700
01:43:20,820 --> 01:43:23,190


1701
01:43:23,400 --> 01:43:27,320


1702
01:43:27,530 --> 01:43:30,610


1703
01:43:30,780 --> 01:43:32,110


1704
01:43:32,280 --> 01:43:34,900


1705
01:43:35,070 --> 01:43:37,990


1706
01:43:38,900 --> 01:43:41,280


1707
01:43:41,490 --> 01:43:43,530


1708
01:43:43,740 --> 01:43:45,530


1709
01:43:45,690 --> 01:43:46,780


1710
01:44:00,240 --> 01:44:01,490


1711
01:44:02,110 --> 01:44:03,440


1712
01:44:03,610 --> 01:44:05,900


1713
01:44:06,070 --> 01:44:08,820


1714
01:44:09,320 --> 01:44:11,360


1715
01:44:11,570 --> 01:44:14,110


1716
01:44:17,240 --> 01:44:19,360


1717
01:44:20,320 --> 01:44:22,860


1718
01:44:23,070 --> 01:44:26,070


1719
01:44:40,780 --> 01:44:44,780


1720
01:44:44,940 --> 01:44:46,530


1721
01:44:48,110 --> 01:44:51,110


1722
01:44:51,280 --> 01:44:55,740


1723
01:44:58,280 --> 01:45:01,900


1724
01:45:04,530 --> 01:45:08,280


1725
01:45:11,820 --> 01:45:13,900


1726
01:45:14,070 --> 01:45:18,070


1727
01:45:18,240 --> 01:45:21,440


1728
01:45:21,610 --> 01:45:22,990


1729
01:45:23,150 --> 01:45:25,030


1730
01:45:25,190 --> 01:45:27,860


1731
01:45:28,030 --> 01:45:29,440


1732
01:45:29,610 --> 01:45:31,820


1733
01:45:35,190 --> 01:45:37,530


1734
01:45:37,690 --> 01:45:40,570


1735
01:45:40,740 --> 01:45:43,280


1736
01:45:43,490 --> 01:45:44,990


1737
01:45:45,150 --> 01:45:47,690


1738
01:45:52,360 --> 01:45:54,610


1739
01:45:56,190 --> 01:45:58,280


1740
01:46:00,150 --> 01:46:02,820


1741
01:46:02,990 --> 01:46:06,190


1742
01:46:06,360 --> 01:46:09,240


1743
01:46:09,400 --> 01:46:11,570


1744
01:46:11,740 --> 01:46:13,320


1745
01:46:13,490 --> 01:46:15,030


1746
01:46:15,190 --> 01:46:17,900


1747
01:46:18,070 --> 01:46:21,320


1748
01:46:28,740 --> 01:46:30,690


1749
01:46:30,860 --> 01:46:33,400


1750
01:46:33,570 --> 01:46:36,240


1751
01:46:36,400 --> 01:46:40,530


1752
01:46:40,690 --> 01:46:43,860


1753
01:46:44,030 --> 01:46:47,860


1754
01:46:48,030 --> 01:46:50,280


1755
01:46:50,440 --> 01:46:53,320


1756
01:46:55,940 --> 01:46:58,400


1757
01:47:02,820 --> 01:47:04,400


1758
01:47:04,570 --> 01:47:08,740


1759
01:47:08,900 --> 01:47:13,070


1760
01:47:21,070 --> 01:47:23,320


1761
01:47:26,240 --> 01:47:28,150


1762
01:47:32,780 --> 01:47:34,820


1763
01:47:36,360 --> 01:47:38,820


1764
01:47:43,990 --> 01:47:45,440


1765
01:47:45,610 --> 01:47:47,650


1766
01:47:47,820 --> 01:47:50,900


1767
01:47:51,070 --> 01:47:52,780


1768
01:47:53,360 --> 01:47:55,610


1769
01:47:55,780 --> 01:47:57,280


1770
01:47:58,820 --> 01:48:00,150


1771
01:48:01,110 --> 01:48:02,940


1772
01:48:15,490 --> 01:48:17,570


1773
01:48:17,740 --> 01:48:19,820


1774
01:48:19,990 --> 01:48:21,030


1775
01:48:22,400 --> 01:48:24,900


1776
01:48:25,070 --> 01:48:26,400


1777
01:48:26,570 --> 01:48:28,070


1778
01:48:28,240 --> 01:48:30,530


1779
01:48:30,690 --> 01:48:31,940


1780
01:48:32,110 --> 01:48:34,320


1781
01:48:35,030 --> 01:48:36,440


1782
01:48:36,610 --> 01:48:39,190


1783
01:48:39,360 --> 01:48:42,030


1784
01:48:42,190 --> 01:48:45,070


1785
01:48:45,070 --> 01:48:49,070


1786
01:48:51,070 --> 01:48:55,070


1787
01:48:55,070 --> 01:48:59,070


1788
01:48:59,070 --> 01:49:04,070


